klook.com 2019-07-06

# Klook Travel

Klook Travel Technology Limited ('Klook', 'we', 'us', 'our') are committed to protecting and respecting your personal data privacy and complying with data protection principles and provisions under applicable laws.

We may collect, process, use and disclose your information when you use this website www.klook.com and/or the Klook App (together, 'Klook Platform') and the services offered by Klook or the third party operators (the'Operators') through Klook Platform (the 'Services') as described in this Privacy Policy. 'You' and 'your' when used in this Privacy Policy includes any person who accesses Klook Platform or use the Services.

This Privacy Policy sets out the basis and terms upon which Klook collects, processes, uses and/or discloses your information that is obtained from you when you access Klook Platform and/or use the Services. Such information may include personal information relating to or linked to a specific individual such as name, residential address, telephone number, email address, travel document information or any such information we have requested and you have provided through Klook Platform ('Personal Information').

**Please read this Privacy Policy carefully.** By visiting Klook Platform, you are consenting to the collection, processing, usage and disclosure of your Personal Information as set out in this Privacy Policy.

  * **Scope of Terms**

    * • Klook reserves the right to update, amend or modify the terms of this Privacy Policy or any part of it without prior notice, and your continued access of Klook Platform or use of the Services signifies your acceptance of the updated, amended or modified Privacy Policy, unless if the changes reduce your rights in which case we will ask for your consent. If you do not agree to all the terms and conditions in this Privacy Policy and/or any subsequent updates, amendments or modifications thereto, you must stop accessing or otherwise using Klook Platform and the Services.
    * • Accordingly, please visit this page if you wish to access and view the current version of this Privacy Policy.
  * **Collection of Information**

    * We may collect Personal Information about you that you provide to us while using Klook Platform and information about how you use Klook Platform including when you open your user account ('User Account'), visit Klook Platform or make reservations for any intended Services or using the Services.

    * 1) Opening Your User Account

      * When you open with us a User Account or amend any information of your User Account, we may collect your Personal Information, such as your name, email address, username, password and telephone number.
    * 2) Visit Klook Platform, Making Reservations for the Services or Using the Services: 

      * (a) When you visit Klook Platform (even you have not registered an User Account or logged in), make reservations for any intended Services or use the Services, we may collect and process certain information (which may contain your Personal Information or may contain non-personally identifiable information but nevertheless linked to your Personal Information) including but not limited to those set out below: Copies of correspondence (whether by e-mail, instant or personal messaging or otherwise) between you and us; and between you and the Operators; 
      * (b) Details of your usage of Klook Platform (including traffic data, location data and length of user sessions); 
      * (c) Feedback on and responses to surveys conducted by Klook relating to the Services and newsletters which may be published, circulated or distributed by Klook; 
      * (d) Information automatically collected and stored in our server or the server of our third party services provider by using or accessing to Klook Platform (including the log-in name and password for your User Account, your computers Internet Protocol (IP) address, browser type, browser information, device information (including unique device identifier), pages visited, previous or subsequent sites visited).
    * 3) When you use your mobile devices to visit Klook Platform, we may collect information about you and your mobile device as stated above. This can include location information if you have consented and configured your mobile device to send us such information or upload photos with location information to Klook Platform. Such location information will be used in the ways and for the purposes as stated in this Privacy Policy. For example, we may use your location to suggest nearby Services during your travel or provide personalised content. You can change your mobile device’s privacy settings at any time to deactivate the function of sharing location information. Please note some features of Klook Platform may be affected if you turn off such location sharing function. Should you have any enquiries about your mobile devices’ privacy settings, we recommend you contacting your mobile services provider or the manufacturer of your device.

    * 4) For your payment safety and to avoid misuse of your credit card information, Klook may ask for your credit card details and a copy of a government issued ID to verify your purchase after payment is complete. For privacy reasons, you will be asked to cover your ID number and your credit card number except for the last 4 digits.

  * **Storage of Information**

    * The Personal Information and other data we collect from you may be transferred to, processed, and stored in our servers or the servers of our third party services providers. Your Personal Information will be stored as long as is necessary to fulfil any of the purposes described in this Privacy Policy, or to comply with any contractual, legal, tax or accounting requirement.
    * When it is no longer necessary for us to process your Personal Information, we will either delete or anonymise the data or, if this is not possible (for example, because your personal information has been stored in backup archives), then we will securely store your personal information.
    * We will endeavor to anonymise or aggregate your data if we intend to use it for analytical purposes or trend analysis.
    * Klook will use reasonable endeavours to maintain appropriate physical, electronic and organisational procedures to ensure that your Personal Information and other data is treated securely and in accordance with this Privacy Policy, and to protect such data against unauthorized access or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of data.
    * Once we have received your information, we will use strict procedures and security features to try to prevent unauthorized access. Klook does not give any representation, warranty or undertaking that the Personal Information you provide to us will be secure at all times, and to the extent Klook has fulfilled its obligations under no circumstances shall Klook be responsible for any losses, damages, costs and expenses which you may suffer or incur arising from unauthorised access to or use of your Personal Information.
    * All payment transactions carried out by us or our chosen third-party provider of payment processing services will be encrypted using online encryption technology. You are responsible for keeping your chosen password confidential and not to share your password with any third party.
  * **Usage of Information**

    * We process the Personal Information collected in as far as necessary for performance of the contract with and providing services to you. Besides, we process the other Personal Information collected on the basis of our legitimate interests, which are the further improvement of the services and for direct marketing purposes.
    * For example, Klook will use Personal Information and other data collected through Klook Platform or when making purchases for the Services to create your User Account, to provide you with the Services, to continually improve Klook Platform and the Services, and to contact you in relation to the Services. This includes using your Personal Information or such other data to achieve faster purchase requests, better customer support and to provide you with timely notice of new Services and special offers.
    * From time to time, we may also make use of your Personal Information to contact you for feedback on your use of Klook Platform, to assist us in improving Klook Platform, or to offer special savings or promotions to you, where you have indicated your consent to receiving such communications. If you would prefer not to receive notices of special savings or promotions, you may simply opt-out from receiving them by replying to us through the hyperlink provided in these notices. 
  * **Disclosure of Information**

    * We may from time to time share and disclose your Personal Information and other data to third parties, some of whom may be located outside your home country. The circumstances under which such sharing and disclosure will take place may include without limitation, the following: 
      * 1) To successfully complete your reservations or otherwise implement our Terms of Use. We may share your information with Operators or third parties who deliver or provide goods and services or otherwise act on our behalf.
      * 2) If you are a visitor, to the relevant Operator in connection with a Services which you have made reservations for or intend to make reservations for.
      * 3) If you are an Operator, to any visitor in connection with the Services you are offering.
      * 4) To our third party service providers (including Google Analytics), which we engage amongst others for the performance of certain services on our behalf, such as web hosting services, data analysis, marketing, market research, and to otherwise provide you with customer service.
      * 5) If and to the extent required by any applicable law, order of court or requests by any governmental authority to make such disclosure.
      * 6) Within the Klook group of companies. In case of a corporate transaction, in connection with the sale, merger, acquisition, or other corporate reorganization or restructuring of our corporation, your Personal Information may be disclosed, shared or transferred to the new controlling entity or its authorised third party for carrying on our business.
      * 7) To our advisors, agencies or other parties concerned in order to protect the rights and property of Klook.
      * 8) In any other case, to any third parties with your prior written consent (and in which case we will make it possible for you to withdraw your consent as easily as it was to provide consent). 
    * We may also share aggregate or anonymous information with relevant third parties, including our advertisers. Such information does not contain any Personal Information and will not identify you personally. However, in some occasions, these third parties may possess information about you or obtain your information from other sources. When they combine such information with our aggregate information, they may be able to identify you personally.
    * Your Personal Information may be transferred outside of your home country and outside of the European Union, for the abovementioned purposes. If such transfer takes place to a country that does not provide an adequate level of protection, Klook will use reasonable endeavours to ensure that appropriate safeguards are in place.
    * There may be links present on Klook Platform which could result in you leaving Klook Platform and/or being taken to other third party websites. You should note that any Personal Information that you provide to these third party websites are not subject to this Privacy Policy, and Klook is not liable for any losses, damages, costs or expenses which you may suffer or incur in connection with you providing or making available Personal Information or other data to such third party websites.
  * **Cookies**

    * Cookies are widely used in order to make websites work, or work more efficiently. When you visit our Website, we collect some of your Personal Information transmitted to us by your browser via cookies. This enables you to access Klook Platform and helps us to create better user experience for you. You will find more details about cookies and similar technologies that we use, in our [Cookies Policy](https://www.klook.com/cookiepolicy/).
  * **Your rights**

    * You may at all times access, correct or erase your Personal Information through Klook Platform via the user portal, under “My Account”. Alternatively, you may make your data access, correction or erasure request by sending your request by email at support@klook.com.
    * Where mandatory under applicable legislation, you may also request restriction of processing of your Personal Information or object to processing by sending your request or objection by email at support@klook.com. You may also request a copy of the information that we hold about you by sending your request by email at support@klook.com.
    * Please contact us via the contact details mentioned below if you have a complaint regarding the processing of your Personal Information.
    * When handling any of these requests described above, we have the right to check the identity of the requester to ensure that he/she is the person entitled to make the request.
  * **European General Data Protection Regulation**

    * Klook Travel Technology Ltd has designated Klook Travel Technology BV (Weesperstraat 61 1018VN Amsterdam, Netherlands) as its representative in the European Union for the purposes of the European General Data Protection Regulation. If you are within the European Union, you have the right to file a complaint with the appropriate data protection authority.
  * **Enquiries**

    * If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us by email at support@klook.com.

Last updated on: 25th February 2019.

At Klook, we strive to enhance your experience during your trip and using this Website. In general, we use cookies to manage the Website and improve your overall site experience.

Your data privacy and confidentiality are our top priority and we do our very best to safeguard the information you entrusted to us. For more information, you can review our <a style="color:grey" href="/policy">Privacy Notice</a> here. 

This section about cookies sets out the basis and terms upon which Klook uses cookies.

**What are cookies?**

Cookies are widely used in the Internet. They are small text files stored in your browser that contain basic information about your internet use, such as login details and your previous browsing records.

A cookie can be classified in terms of its (i) duration and (ii) the party who places it:

**_(i) Session cookies and Persistent cookies_**

The duration of cookies depends on whether they are session or persistent cookies.

**Session cookies** expire once the browsing session ends.

**Persistent cookies** are saved on your computer or mobile device for a fixed period of time. When you visit a website, your browser will retrieve these cookies so that the website will recognise your device and personalise your site experience according to your previous browsing records.

**_(ii) First-party cookies and Third-party cookies_**

We control and set the scope of **first-party cookies** whereas, we have no control over **third-party cookies**. Third-party cookies are operated by third-party sites in a different domain. Some pages of this Website contain third-party cookies in the form of embedded content, such as JavaScript and API.

**_Why do we use cookies?_**

We are committed to providing you with a safe, efficient and customised service. To reach this goal, we use cookies to:<p></p>

  * •&nbsp;ensure the efficient functioning of this Website;
  * •&nbsp;evaluate how this Website is accessed and used;
  * •&nbsp;analyse what destinations are popular among visitors;
  * •&nbsp;determine your eligibility for campaigns and promotions;
  * •&nbsp;recommend the places that match your interests; and
  * •&nbsp;improve the content of this Website and enhance user's experience.

We will ensure that cookies will not be used for any purpose other than those described here.

**_What types of cookies do we use?_**

We use four types of cookies, namely "Strictly necessary cookies", "Essential cookies," "Analytics cookies", and "Advertising cookies". Further information on these cookies is set out in the table below:

<figure><table><thead><tr><th style="text-align:left;">Cookies</th><th>Description</th></tr></thead><tbody><tr><td style="text-align:left;">Strictly necessary cookies </td><td>These cookies allow us to manage this Website and ensure it functions properly. They are essential to help you navigate around this Website and provide you with an improved surfing experience.<br>If these cookies are disabled, we will not be in a position to offer you our services.<br> We also use these cookies for fraud detection and prevention purposes. Further, thanks to these cookies, you do not need to log in repeatedly to access different pages once you have logged into this Website. </td></tr><tr><td style="text-align:left;">Analytics cookies </td><td>We use analytics cookies including Google Analytics and other analytics tools to gather anonymous statistical information for: <br>•&nbsp;assessing how our visitors use this Website;<br>•&nbsp;understanding the demographic and location of our visitors;<br>•&nbsp;evaluating how our new products are being received by usersassessing the popularity of our marketing campaign;<br>•&nbsp;enhancing this Website content and service by customising this Website for you. <br>Based on the anonymous data collected, these analytics tools will generate trend analysis and compile reports to attain the abovementioned purposes. </td></tr><tr><td style="text-align:left;">Advertising cookies</td><td>Advertising cookies enable us to limit the number of times you see the same ad and to ensure that the ad content is relevant to your interests. These cookies, together with an identifier linked to your IP address, can track your activity across various websites and thus display ads in accordance to your preference. </td></tr></tbody></table></figure>

**_Consent to cookies_**

In most cases we will need your consent in order to use cookies on this Website. The exception is where the cookies are strictly necessary in order for us to provide you with a service you have requested, or essential to the inherent functionality of the Website.

Upon your first visit to our Website, you will see a notification banner at the top of the page notifying you about our use of cookies. By continuing to use this Website without changing your settings, you agree to receive all cookies and other data tracking tools. On the other hand, if you do not wish to accept the use of these cookies, you can modify your cookie setting at any time. For more details, please refer to "How can you manage your consent?" section below.

**_How can you manage your consent?_**

You can accept or decline our use of cookies at any time by managing and/or disabling all or some of the cookies from your browser settings. However, by doing so, you may not be able to enjoy the full functionality of this Website.

Cookies settings can normally be found in the preference or settings menu from your browser, for example:

  * •&nbsp;Chrome: Settings -- Advanced -- Content Settings -- Cookies
  * •&nbsp;Safari: Preferences -- Privacy -- Cookies and website data
  * •&nbsp;Firefox: Preferences -- Privacy -- History
  * •&nbsp;Internet Explorer: Internet Options -- Privacy
  * •&nbsp;Opera: Settings -- Privacy & security -- Cookies

Last Updated : 3 October 2018

We’ll refund **double the difference** …if you find a cheaper price!

We know that one of the most important things for travelers is getting a fair price and not feeling ripped off. That’s why we constantly monitor our pricing to ensure that you get the best price available online and at your destination. We also make it a point to display honest pricing on all our deals, including all extra charges and taxes so you'll never have to worry about additional costs.

We’re so confident about our pricing that if you find a better price, we’ll refund DOUBLE the difference! 

  * **So, if you:** **
    * • Find a lower price (in the same currency) for the same tour or activity and notify us within 48 hours of booking, or
**
    * **• Arrive at your destination and find your booked tour or activity offered for a lower price**

you can send us the details and we'll refund double the difference in the form of Klook Credits OR we’ll refund the full price difference to your card.

Yup, you read us right!

  * **How to request a refund?**

    * It's simple and easy: obtain proof of the lower rate (receipt, price list, flyer, website, screenshot etc.), and email us at support@klook.com with your name and booking number. We’ll add double the difference value to your account as Klook Credits, or refund the full price difference direct to your card.
  * **Terms & Conditions**

    * The ‘same tour or activity’ means that all inclusions and itineraries must be the same as the activity booked from Klook, this includes currency, number of people, scheduling, operator, pick up locations, ticket usage (printed or mobile voucher), ticket validity (fixed date or open date), package booked, ticket type, instant or non instant confirmation, etc. The product may be sold by another channel, however it must be the same product as offered by Klook.

      * • Products must be sold by official channels and registered travel agencies.
      * • This guarantee does not include any city or airport transfers.
      * • This guarantee does not include multi-day tours.
      * • Due to select operator restrictions, 'Klook Price Guarantee' only applies to activities that display this tag on the activity page.
      * • Klook's Best Price Guarantee covers retail rates available to the general public. This does not include discounts you may receive (or be eligible for) from third-party organizations or special offers made as part of a membership program, corporate discount, promotion, group or rewards program.
      * • If you find a cheaper price before arriving at your destination, you must notify us within 48 hours of your original booking, or have dated proof that the cheaper price was found within 48 hours of your original booking.
      * • Klook reserves the right to verify details of the lower price where possible, all refund decisions will be made at the sole discretion of Klook.
      * • Refunds of the price difference will be transacted to the credit card used in the original booking.
      * • If you used Klook credits or a promo code when making your booking, you will receive a refund of twice the difference from the original Klook price, not the discounted price
